<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aryan Arora</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aryan Arora</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Joining a LabLab AI Hackathon Can Boost Your Career</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blogs/how_joining_a_lablab_ai_hackathon_can_boost_your_career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blogs/how_joining_a_lablab_ai_hackathon_can_boost_your_career/</guid>
      <description>Unleashing Career Potential with LabLab AI Hackathons Participating in LabLab AI hackathons provides a unique opportunity to unleash your career potential in the field of artificial intelligence. The hackathons offer a platform for AI professionals and enthusiasts to come together, collaborate, and innovate with cutting-edge AI technologies. By joining these events, you can expand your skill set, network with industry experts, and gain hands-on experience in developing AI solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Your Health Monitoring System with Arduino, Streamlit, and GPT-3.5 Turbo🌡️💻</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blogs/building-your-health-monitoring-system-with-arduino-streamlit-and-gpt-3.5-turbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blogs/building-your-health-monitoring-system-with-arduino-streamlit-and-gpt-3.5-turbo/</guid>
      <description>Building Your Health Monitoring System with Arduino, Streamlit, and GPT-3.5 Turbo🌡️💻 Welcome back to our series on thinking like a computer science student! In this second blog, we&amp;rsquo;re diving deep into the realm of health monitoring systems using Arduino, Streamlit, and GPT-3.5 Turbo. Get ready for an exhilarating journey as we construct our very own HealthMate! 🚀&#xA;🏥 Introduction Have you ever envisioned having a personalized health companion? Well, dream no more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Your Portfolio Site with Hugo and GitHub</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blogs/how_to_build_portfolio_website_using_hugo_and_github_actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blogs/how_to_build_portfolio_website_using_hugo_and_github_actions/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the first part of our &amp;ldquo;How to Think Like a Computer Science Student&amp;rdquo; series! Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to create a professional portfolio site using Hugo, a powerful static site generator, and automating the deployment process with GitHub Actions.&#xA;Why Hugo? Meet Hugo, a fast and flexible static site generator written in Go. Its simplicity and flexibility make it an excellent choice for building a lightweight and highly customizable portfolio site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
